The Silent Flyer is a adventure film directed by William James Craft.
This movie was billed as a thriller with ice boats,
dynamite, and a dog that saves the day.
The original movie has been lost.
It survives as a 90 second trailer.
This trailer is also available on "More Treasures of
the AFA" without the video game music.
Lloyd Darrell, posing as Bill Smith, played by Malcolm McGregor.
Helen Corliss, played by Louise Lorraine.
John Corliss, played by George B. Williams.
Jack Hutchins, played by Albert J. Smith.
Benjamin Darrell, played by Anders Randolf.
Mrs. Darrell, played by Edith Yorke.
The Silent Flyer is a 1926 10-episode (chapter) American
adventure film serial directed by William James Craft.
The film serial was sold to Universal Pictures for $75,000 with the
resulting funds used in the founding of Mascot Pictures.